Sat Jan 16 11:53:29 2021

DUEL_ONCE_TEST:
  Python version: 3.8.5
  DUEL_ONCE simulates a single duel between combatants
  who fire alternately at each other, with known probabilities
  of hitting the other.

  In this example, the one shot probabilities are:
  Player[0]: 0.1
  Player[1]: 0.15

  Result of this duel:
  Player 1 survived after 10 turns

DUEL_SIMULATION_TEST:
  Python version: 3.8.5
  DUEL_SIMULATION repeatedly simulates a duel between combatants
  who fire alternately at each other, with known probabilities
  of hitting the other.

  In this example, the one shot probabilities are:
  Player[0]: 0.1
  Player[1]: 0.15

  The number of duels to fight is 1000

  Result of the duels:
  Player 0 winning percentage is 0.394
  Player 1 winning percentage is 0.606

  The average number of shots fired was 8.052
Sat Jan 16 11:53:29 2021
